大家好，我们开始吧，我想谈谈一个叫做
alright hello everyone let's get started
I want to talk about a system called
今天的证书透明性与大多数
certificate transparency today and this
is a bit of a departure from most of the
到目前为止，我们讨论的主题是关于分布式系统的
topics we talked about so far we've
talked about distributed systems that
是真正的封闭系统，所有参与者都是值得信赖的
are really closed systems where all the
participants are trustworthy they're all
可能是由同一类型的相互信任的组织运行的
maybe be run being run by the same sort
of mutually trusting organization like
这样，您就知道您只是假设在皇家空军的各个级别
rafters that way you know you just
assume at the RAF's tiers do what
他们本来应该做的，但是那里也有很多系统
they're supposed to do but there's also
plenty of systems out there particularly
系统建立了一个互联网规模，其中系统是开放的，任何人
systems sort of built an internet scale
where the systems are open and anyone
可以成为积极的参与者，我的意思是在一些大型系统中
can participate being active participant
I mean in some big systems out there and
如果您以这种方式构建完全开放的系统，那么通常不会
if you build systems that are completely
open in that way there's often no single
所有人都愿意信任的权威机构
universally trusted Authority that
everybody is willing to trust to run the
系统或保护它，这就是每个人都有可能
system or to protect it that is
everybody you sort of potentially
互相怀疑其他所有人，如果是这种情况，您必须
mutually suspicious of everyone else and
if that's the situation you have to be
能够从互不信任的部分中构建有用的系统
able to build useful systems out of
mutually distrusting pieces and this
在任何种类的互联网开放系统中进行信任和安全性排序
makes in any sort of internet wide open
systems to make trust and security sort
设计分布式系统时遇到的顶级系统问题
of top level systems issues when you're
thinking about designing a distributed
系统，因此构建开放系统时最基本的问题是何时
system so the most basic question when
you're building an open system is when
我正在与另一台计算机或您需要知道的其他人说话
I'm talking to another computer or
another person you need to know are you
与正确的其他计算机通话，或者您在与正确的网站通话，以及
talking to the right other computer or
are you talking to the right website and
这个问题实际上几乎是无法解决的，事实证明
this problem is actually close to
unsolvable it turns out there's really
有很多解决方案，但没有一个真的能很好地解决问题，但这是
there's lots of solutions and none
really work that well but it is the
证书透明性是当今主题试图解决的问题
problem that certificate transparency
today's topic is trying to help with the
事实证明，今天的物质在整个过程中会有些倒退
material today ties sort of backwards in
the course to consistency it turns out
证书透明度所做的很多工作是确保
that a lot of what certificate
transparency do doing is ensuring that
各方看到有关证书的相同信息
all parties see
the same information about certificates
这是一个真正的一致性问题，该材料也与区块链相关
that's a real consistency issue and this
material also ties forward to blockchain
像区块链这样的系统，这就是我们下周要讨论的
systems like blockchain which is what we
talk talking about next week a
证书透明性是相对较少的非加密货币用途之一
certificate transparency is among the
relatively few non cryptocurrency uses
像设计这样的区块链的概念，所以作为介绍，我想开始
of a blockchain like design alright so
by way of introduction I want to start
随时随地通过网络安全来应对网络上的情况
with the situation on the web with web
security at any rate as it existed
1995年之前的证书之前，所以这是1995年的，特别是
before 1995 before certificates so this
is for 1995 and in particular there was
在那些日子里，人们担心的是一种攻击
a there was a kind of attack in those
days that people were worried about
称为中间人攻击，这是人在
called a man-in-the-middle attacks this
is man in
中间，这是一类攻击类型的名称，所以您知道
middle and this is a name for a class of
attacks style of attack so you know the
在那些日子里建立的就是你有互联网，有人在跑
set up in those days is you have the
internet and you have people running
浏览器和我们的计算机连接在一起
browsers
um sitting with our computer attached to
互联网坐在我电脑前的任何人
the Internet
anyone sitting in front of my computer I
想和一个特定的服务器对话，我想做的就是与
want to talk to a specific server
exposing what I want to do is talk to
gmail.com对，通常来说，您会与我联系DNS系统吗？
gmail.com right and ordinarily I would
you know maybe contact the DNS system I
作为用户，我也许会输入gmail.com我会知道我想要什么
would as a user I maybe type gmail.com I
would sort of know what it was I wanted
说出Li gmail.com的名字，我的浏览器会和DNS服务器说出什么
to talk to name Li gmail.com my browser
would talk to DNS servers say what's
gmail.com，它将回复一个我连接了该IP地址的IP地址，
gmail.com it would reply with a IP
address I connected that IP address and
您知道我需要进行身份验证，所以我可能会输入密码
you know I need to authenticate myself
so I'd probably type my password to
从Gmail转到Gmail的网站，然后Gmail会向我显示没有任何形式的电子邮件
Gmail to Gmail's website and then Gmail
would show me my email without some kind
为了安全起见，这个系统实际上很容易被攻击和转向
of story for security this system is
actually quite easy to attack and turn
易于攻击，一种攻击方式是所谓的“攻击”
out to be easy to attack and the one
style of attack is that what's called a
中间人攻击，其中一些邪恶的人设置了另一个Web服务器，该服务器
man-in-the-middle attack where some evil
person sets up a another web server that
提供与Gmail Web服务器类似的页面，就像您上次登录时一样
serves pages that look just like Gmail
web servers like the last for your login
和密码正确，然后攻击者可能会拦截我的DNS数据包或
and password right and then the attacker
would maybe intercept my DNS packets or
只是猜测我什么时候会发送DNS数据包并提出虚假答复
just guess when I would have sent a DNS
packet and come up with a fake reply
而不是提供真实gmail.com服务器的真实IP地址
that instead of providing the real IP
address of the real gmail.com server
将提供攻击者的假冒计算机的电子邮件地址，然后
would provide the email address of ma of
the attackers fake computer and then the
用户的浏览器而不是与Gmail通话实际上对他们来说是未知的
user's browser instead of talking to
Gmail would actually unknown to them be
与攻击者计算机交谈，攻击者计算机将提供一个网站
talking to the attackers computer the
attackers computer would provide a web
页面看起来就像一个登录页面，用户类型是路径日志和密码，以及
page looks just like a login page user
types are paths log and a password and
现在，攻击者的计算机可以将其转发给您的真实Gmail登录名。
now the attackers computer can forward
that to the real Gmail login for you of
当然您不知道您知道将当前的收件箱还给攻击者
course you don't know that you know get
your current inbox back to the attackers
大概会与您的密码一起记录下来然后发送的计算机
computer which presumably records it
along with your password and then sends
您的收件箱或浏览器中的任何内容，这可以使您知道是否可以
your inbox or whatever to the browser
and this allows a you know if you can
进行攻击者计算机可以记录的这种中间人攻击
execute this kind of man-in-the-middle
attack the attackers computer can record
您的密码记录了您的电子邮件，您将永远不再明智
your password record your email and
you'll never be the wiser
以及SSL和HTTPS上的证书之前
and
before certificates on SSL and HTTPS
真的没有防御这个妈妈的办法，所以这是那个男人
there was really no defense against this
mom okay so this is the man in the
中间攻击，这里的攻击者是中间的人，就像
middle attack and this attacker here is
the man in the middle looks just like
与浏览器交谈时，假装浏览器的Gmail是用户，因此
Gmail to the browser pretends to be the
user when talking to Gmail so that it
可以真正从Gmail中获取诱使用户进入的信息
can actually get the information from
Gmail required to trick the user into
认为这真的可以使用Gmail，所以这是90年代中期的攻击
thinking it's really Gmail all right so
this is the attack in the mid-90s people
提出了带有SSL的证书，或者也称为TLS，这就是
came up with certificates with SSL or
it's also called TLS it's what the
协议使用HTTPS链接时使用的安全协议um
protocol the security protocol that
you're using when you use HTTPS links um
而这里的游戏是Gmail通讯将具有一个公共/私有密钥对
and here the game was that Gmail comm
was gonna have a public/private key pair
因此我们只有一个私钥，只有Gmail知道该私钥位于其服务器中，
so we'd have a private key that only
Gmail knows sitting in its server and
然后，当您与用户的连接良好时，您会在需要连接的地方进行连接
then when you connect well your the user
you connect somewhere you ask to connect
到您知道的Gmail，并且为了验证您是否真的在与Gmail通话，
to Gmail you know and in order to verify
that you're really talking to Gmail the
要求使用Gmail的用户证明它确实拥有Gmail是私钥
users going to demand Gmail prove that
it really owns Gmail is private key well
当然，您的浏览器在哪里可以找到Gmail
of course
where does your browser find out Gmail
是Gmail公钥中的私钥，您需要检查该私钥
is private key from your Gmail public
key which is what you need to check that
它确实具有私钥，还有证书的概念
it really has the private key there's
also this notion of certificate
机构和证书，因此在Gmail时会有证书机构
authorities and certificates so there'd
be a certificate authority when Gmail
设置其服务器，它将与证书颁发机构联系
set up its server it would contact the
certificate authority may be on the
电话或通过电子邮件或其他方式说出您知道我想要的证书
phone or by email or something and say
look you know I want a certificate for
DNS名称gmail.com和证书颁发机构会尝试一下
the DNS name gmail.com and the
certificate authority would sort of try
验证哦，是的，要求证书的人确实拥有该名称
to verify that oh yes whoever's asking
for certificate really owns that name
确实是Google或拥有gmail.com的人，如果是，则证书
it really is Google or whoever owns
gmail.com and if so the certificate
当局会提供证明书
authority would provide a certificate
回到gee komm这基本上是什么证书
back to gee
komm which basically what a certificate
包含Web服务器的名称，Web服务器的公共密钥和一个
contains is the name of the web server
the web servers public key and a
由证书颁发机构私人对此证书进行签名
signature over this certificate made
with the certificate authorities private
密钥，因此这是一种可通过检查
key so this is sort of a self-contained
assertion checkable by checking the
证书颁发机构对公众的声明进行签名
signature an assertion by the
certificate authority that the public
gmail.com的密钥确实是这个公共密钥gmail.com服务器，我只保留一个
key of gmail.com is really this public
key gmail.com server would I just keep a
如果您使用HTTPS首先连接到gmail.com服务器，则证书的副本
copy of the certificate if you connect
to gmail.com server with HTTPS the first
它所做的是将您的证书发回给您
thing it does is sends you back this
certificate at this point is just a
由于gmail.com愿意将证书颁发给
certificate right now of course since
gmail.com is willing to give it to
任何人都是证书本身根本没有怀孕，这是相当公开的
anybody it's the certificate itself is
not at all pregnant it's quite public
然后浏览器会发送一些信息，例如
and then the browser would send some
information like a random number for
以服务器为例，并要求其使用其私钥对其进行签名，然后
example to the server and ask it to sign
it with its private key and then the
浏览器可以使用证书中的公钥随机检查
browser can check using the public key
in the certificate that the random
号码已经运行，并且记住确实是由私钥签名的
number is ran and remember was really
signed by the private key that's
与证书中的公钥相关联，因此无论谁
associated with the public key in the
certificate and therefore that whoever
所谈论的实际上是证书颁发机构认为的实体
it's talking to is really the entity
that the certificate authority believes
是gmail.com，现在可以了，这就是为什么这使得中间人
is gmail.com all right and now the
reason why this makes man-in-the-middle
攻击更难的是，是的，您知道您可以设置一个流氓服务器，
attacks much harder is that yeah you
know you can set up a rogue server that
看起来就像Gmail一样平静，也许您甚至可以破解DNS系统，
looks just like Gmail calm and maybe you
can even hack the DNS system indeed you
如果您足够聪明，功能仍然强大，可以入侵DNS系统以告知
still can if you're sufficiently clever
powerful hack the DNS system to tell
人们的浏览器，哦，他们应该转到您的服务器而不是gmail.com，但是
people's browsers that oh they should go
to your server instead of gmail.com but
一旦有人的浏览器联系您的服务器
once somebody's browser contacts your
server
您大概不会能够出示如下证明：
you're not presumably going to be able
to produce a certificate that says but
您可以生成Gmail证书，然后生成Gmail证书作为Gmail的
you you can produce Gmail certificate
but then Gmail certificate as Gmail's
公钥您的服务器没有私钥，因此您可以
public key your server doesn't have
their private key so you can
签署浏览器向您发送的挑战，大概是因为您不是真正的
sign the challenge the browser sent you
and presumably since you're not the real
Google，而不是真正的Gmail，您将无法说服
Google and not the real Gmail you're not
going to be able to persuade a
证书颁发机构为您提供将gmail comm与关联的证书
certificate authority to give you a
certificate associating gmail comm with
您的公钥，该单位，因此该证书计划
your public key that unit and so this
certificate scheme made
中间人攻击要困难得多，而且您知道他们确实是
man-in-the-middle attacks quite a bit
harder and you know indeed they are
现在因为证书还可以，所以难度更大了，尽管如此
quite a bit harder now because of
certificates okay so it turns out though
人们现在对证书计划有很多经验
that the certificate scheme as people
now have a lot of experience with it
拥有将近25年的经验，所以我们现在知道有些事情
almost 25 years experience within so we
now know there's some kind of things
原来是在想象中会出现几个错误
that go wrong it was originally imagined
that there would just be a couple of
值得信赖的证书颁发机构，可以很好地检查
trustworthy certificate authorities who
would do a good job of checking that
请求真的来自他们声称来自谁的人，如果有人
request really came from who they
claimed to come from that if somebody
为gmail.com要求该证书颁发机构提供的证书
asked for a certificate for gmail.com
that this certificate authorities would
实际上确实验证了该请求来自所有者gmail.com
indeed actually verified that the
request came from the owner gmail.com
并没有将证书分发给随机人进行gmail comp，但是事实证明
and not hand out certificates to random
people for gmail comp but it that turns
对Google来说非常具有挑战性，也许您可​​以说服此证书
out to be very challenging for google
maybe you can convince this certificate
权威可以说服自己来自Google的请求，但您知道
authority can convince itself that a
request comes from Google but you know
对于仅XCOM而言，很难拥有可靠的证书颁发机构
for just XCOM that's very hard to have a
certificate authority reliably able to
说哦，天哪，这个要求真的来自真正拥有自己的人
say oh yeah gosh this request really
came from the person who really does own
DMS名称XCOM可以解决的一个更糟糕的问题是，
the DMS name XCOM all right a worse
problem is that while originally they
设想只有几个证书颁发机构
were envisioned there'd be only a few
certificate authority there are now
数以百计的证书颁发机构在那里，以及任何
literally hundreds of certificate
authorities out there and any
证书颁发机构可以生成任何名称的证书，并且确实可以
certificate authority can generate a
certificate for any name and indeed may
希望您被允许更改证书颁发机构（如果您是
want to you're allowed to change
certificate authorities if you're a
网站所有者，您可以将证书颁发机构更改为您喜欢的任何人，因此
website owner you can change certificate
authority to whoever you like so there's
没有哪个证书颁发机构对其权力有限制
no sense in which certificate
authorities have limits on their powers
他们可以任何证书颁发机构可以产生任何证书，现在浏览器
they can any certificate authority can
produce any certificate and now browsers
您是否知道有几百个证书颁发机构，这意味着
have you know there's a couple hundred
certificate authorities and that means
每个浏览器内置的浏览器（例如Chrome或Firefox）或内置的某些内容
that each browser has built into it like
Chrome or Firefox or something has built
其中所有证书的公钥列表共几百种
into it a list of the public keys of all
the certificate all couple hundred sort
良好的权威，如果其中任何一个人已经签署了由网络产生的证书
good authorities and if any of them sign
has signed a certificate produced by web
服务器证书可以接受的结果是，已经有
server certificates acceptable the
result of this is that there have been
证书颁发机构多次产生伪造证书的事件
multiple incidents of certificate
authorities producing bogus certificates
产生证明他们是Google的证书或
that is producing certificates that said
they were certificate for Google or
Gmail或其他真实公司，但实际上是完全发布给某人的
Gmail or some other real company but
were actually issued to someone totally
否则，绝对不会颁发Google名称之一的证书，但不会颁发
else absolutely not issued certificate
for one of Google's names but not issued
给Google发布给其他类似的人，您知道有时这种情况只会发生
to Google issued to someone else like
and you know sometimes this happens just
因为上级当局没有意识到他们在做
by mistake because superior Authority
doesn't realize that they're doing the
错误的事情，有时实际上是非常恶意的，我的意思是
wrong thing and sometimes it's actually
quite malicious I mean there have
当然是颁发给只想窥探的人的证书
certainly been certificates issued to
people who just wanted to snoop on
人们的交通和中间人攻击，
people's traffic and mount
man-in-the-middle attacks and did
在今天的读物中提到了“山人中间攻击”中的几个
Mountain Man the middle attacks today's
readings are mentioned a couple of these
事件，它们特别令人困扰，因为它们很难
incidents and they're particularly
troubling because they're hard to
阻止，因为证书颁发机构太多，而并非全部
prevent because there's so many
certificate authorities and not all of
他们，尽管对不起，最后一个问题是
them
although sorry the last question let was
最后一行插入框是证书上方的签名
the last line insert box it's a
signature over the certificate by the
先生提示由证书颁发机构使用证书
sir tip using by the certificate
authorities using the certificate
当局的私钥好，所以出现了假事件
authorities private key okay so there
have been incidents of bogus
证书真正的网站（如Google）的证书颁发给
certificates certificates for real
websites like Google issued to totally
错误的人和那些证书被滥用，目前尚不清楚
the wrong people and those certificates
have been abused and it's not clear how
修复证书颁发机构系统本身以防止它们发生，因为
to fix the certificate authority system
itself to prevent them because there's
如此众多的证书颁发机构，他们真的让您无法期望
so many certificate authorities and they
really you just can't expect that
他们将是完全可靠的，所以我们该怎么办
they're going to be completely reliable
so what can we do about this one
可能只有一个在线的所有有效数据库
possibility would be to have a single
online database of all valid
证书，以便当您知道浏览器时浏览器Comcast网站web
certificates so that when a browser
you know browser Comcast websites web
现场出示您知道或可能有效的证书，那么也许您
site hands at a certificate you know
might or might be valid then maybe you
可以想象浏览器将联系全局有效证书数据库
could imagine the browser would contact
the global valid certificate database
ins化验确实是证书，是连续颁发的假证书
ins assays this really is certificate
a bogus certificate issued by a row
证书颁发机构，问题是该方法有很多问题
certificate authority um the problem is
as many problems with that approach one
尚不清楚您如何才能正确区分有效人
is it's still not clear how you can how
anybody can distinguish valid correctly
伪造证书颁发的证书，因为通常您只是
issued certificates from bogus
certificates because typically you just
不知道谁是DNS名称的正确所有者，此外，您还需要
don't know who the proper owner of DNS
names it is furthermore you need to
允许证书所有者更改证书颁发机构或更新其证书颁发机构
allow certificate owners to change
certificate authorities or renew their
证书，否则他们可能会丢失其私钥并需要新证书
certificates or they may lose their
private key and need a new certificate
取代他们以前的想法，因为使用了新的公钥/私钥对
to replace their older to think because
using a new public/private key pair so
人们的证书一直在变化，甚至在技术上或
people's certificates change all the
time and finally even if technically or
可以区分伪造的正确证书
were possible to distinguish correct
certificates from bogus ones
没有任何人会相信这样做的实体，您知道
there's no entity that everybody would
trust to do it you know everybody in the
世界上那些你认识的中国伊朗人你知道的美国人
world those you know the Chinese
Iranians the Americans you know there's
没有一个他们都信任的服装，这就是为什么
not any one outfit that they all trust
and that's the root reason why there's
这么多的证书颁发机构，所以我们真的不能您真的不能期望
so many certificate authorities so we
really can't you really can't expect
只有一个票据交换所可以准确地区分有效货币
there to be a single Clearing House that
accurately distinguishes between valid
和无效的证书，但是什么是证书颁发机构证书
and invalid certificates however what
certificate authority certificate
透明所做的就是实质上不尽力而为
transparency doing is doing is
essentially try not do the best that
您是否有可能知道朝数据库的最长一步
it's possible to do you know the longest
step it can towards a database of the
完整的可信赖证书，所以现在我将概述
holid trustworthy certificates so now
I'm gonna give an overview of the
证书透明度的一般策略证书样式
general strategy of certificate
transparency the style of certificate
透明度在于这是一个审计系统，因为很难
transparency is that it's an audit
system because it's so hard hard to
无法仅仅确定此人是否拥有名称证书
impossible to just decide does this
person own a name a certificate
透明度不是建立防止不良事件发生的系统
transparency isn't a building a system
that prevents bad things from happening
这将要求您能够立即检测到
which would require you to be able to
detect right away that as
证书是伪造的，而是证书透明度
certificate was bogus instead
certificate transparency is going to
启用审核，这将是导致所有信息被删除的系统
enable audit that is it'll it's a system
to cause all the information to be
公开，以便可以由关心它的人检查
public so that it can be inspected by
people who care that is it's gonna if
你知道也许有人会继续允许人们签发伪造证书，但是
you know maybe people it'll still allow
people to issue bogus certificates but
这将确保这些证书是公开的，并且每个人都可以看到它们
it's gonna insure those certificates are
public and that everybody can see them
包括拥有虚假名字的人
including whoever it is that owns the
name that the name that's in the bogus
证书，因此可以解决预证书问​​题
certificate and so this fixes the
problem with the pre certificate
证书颁发机构可以伪造的透明系统
transparency system where certificate
authorities could issue bogus
证书，没人会知道，甚至可以把它们交给受害者
certificates and no one would ever know
and they could even give them to victim
一些受害浏览器会被他们欺骗，仍然是
a few victim browsers who would be
tricked by them and still because
证书通常不公开，他们可能有人可以证书
certificates aren't generally public
they could somebody could a certificate
当局可以为任何人为Google颁发伪造的证书，或者
authority could issue a bogus
certificate for anybody for Google or
微软和谷歌微软可能永远都不会意识到这一点，
Microsoft and Google Microsoft might
never realize it and the incidents that
被发现通常只是偶然发现的，不是因为
have come to light have generally been
discovered only by accident not because
他们有点前途未卜，所以不再依赖
they were sort of foredoomed to be
discovered so instead of relying on
意外发现伪造证书证书透明度
accidental discovery of bogus
certificates certificate transparency
它将迫使他们陷入困境
it's going to sort of force them into
the light where they is much easier to
再次注意它们，因此它具有某种审核风格或nada而不是预防措施
notice them again so it has a sort of
audit flavor or nada not a prevention
味道还可以，所以我们的基本结构还是gmail.com或其他服务
flavor okay so the basic structure again
we have gmail.com or some other service
像往常一样想要一张证书，他们会问
that wants a certificate as usual
they're gonna ask someone of the
证书Web服务器首次设置时的证书的数百个CAS
hundreds of CAS for a certificate when
when when the cert web servers first set
上，所以我们要索取证书，证书颁发机构要发送
up so we're gonna ask a certificate and
the certificate authority is gonna send
该证书返回到Web服务器，因为当然是
this certificate back to the web server
because of course is the web server that
向浏览器提供证书，同时通过证书
gives a certificate to the browser and
at the same time though the certificate
权威机构将证书或等效信息的副本发送给
authority is going to send a copy of the
certificate or equivalent information to
一种透明的vlog服务器
a sort
Transparency vlog server there's gonna
真实系统中透明地存在多个独立证书
the real system there's multiple
independent certificate transparently
日志服务器，我可以假设只有一个，所以这是您需要的一些服务
log servers i can assume there's just
one so this is some service that you
知道我们没有证明我们不必信任证书
know we don't have turns out we're not
gonna have to trust the certificate
当局会将其证书发送到该证书日志服务
authorities gonna send it certificate to
this certificate log service which has
一直在维护所有已颁发证书或所有已颁发证书的日志
been maintaining a log of all issued
certificates or all ones that
证书颁发机构已告知它何时获得新证书
certificate authorities have told it
about when it gets a new certificate
它将附加到其日志中，因此您可能知道有数百万
it's gonna append it to its log so this
you know might have millions of
一段时间后，当浏览器和某些人想要
certificates in it after a while now
when the browser and some human wants to
与您知道他们交谈过的网站进行对话建立了一个HTTPS连接
talk to a website they you know they
talk did set up an HTTPS connection to
Gmail Gmail将证书发回给他们，浏览器将发送该证书
Gmail Gmail sends them a certificate
back and the browser's gonna send that
证书发送到证书日志服务器，请参阅
certificate to the certificate log
server see is this certificate in the
日志中有difficut日志服务器会说是或否是他们的证书在
log there's difficut log servers gonna
say yes or no is their certificate in
现在登录，如果是，则浏览器将继续并立即使用它
the log now and if it is then the
browser will go ahead and use it now the
它在您知道的日志中并不意味着它不是假的
fact that it's in the log you know
doesn't mean it's not bogus right
因为任何证书颁发机构（包括那里的证书颁发机构）
because any certificate authority
including the ones that are out there
恶意或运行不当的证书颁发机构可以插入
that are malicious or badly run any
certificate authority can insert a
证书进入日志系统，因此可能会诱骗用户使用
certificate into the log system and
therefore perhaps trick users into using
所以到目前为止，我们还没有建立防止滥用的系统，但是
it so for so far we haven't built a
system that prevents abuse however it is
除非在日志中没有浏览器将不使用证书，
the case that no browser will use a
certificate unless it's in the log so at
gmail将与CT系统一起运行时，同时调用监视器和
the same time gmail is going to run up
with the CT system calls a monitor and
现在，只要假设有一台显示器
for now well
just assume that there's a monitor
与每个网站相关联，因此该监控器还会定期与
associated with every website so this
monitor periodically also talks to the
证书日志服务器是一种资产，请给我您的日志副本，或者实际上是您
certificate log servers an asset please
give me a copy of your log or really you
知道请给我一份自我以来已添加的新内容的副本
know please give me a copy of whatever
new has been added to your long since I
最后一个问题，这意味着显示器将要建立起来
last asked and that means that the
monitor is going to build up it's going
知道其中的每个证书就足够了
to be aware of every single certificate
that's going to be enough that's in the
日志，而且还因为该监视器与Gmail关联，因此该监视器知道
log and but also because the monitor is
associated with Gmail the monitor knows
Gmail的正确证书是什么，如果某些流氓证书颁发机构
what Gmail's correct certificate is so
if some rogue certificate authority
为Gmail颁发证书，而不是Gmail本身要求的证书
issues a certificate for Gmail it's not
the one that Gmail itself asked for then
Gmail的监视器会在证书日志中绊倒它，因为Gmail的监视器
Gmail's monitor will stumble across it
in the certificate log because Gmail's
监视器现在当然知道流氓Gmail的正确证书
monitor knows Gmail's correct
certificate now of course the rogue
证书颁发机构不必将其证书发送到证书
certificate authority doesn't have to
send its certificate to the certificate
日志系统，但在这种情况下，当您知道浏览器时可能是偶然的
log system but in that case when
browsers you know maybe accidentally
连接到攻击者的Web服务器，攻击者将刷服务器提供
connect to the attackers web server and
the attacker would swipe server gives
他们伪造的证书，如果他们没有把它放在日志中，那么
them the bogus certificate if they
haven't put it in the log then the
浏览器不会相信它，并且将中止连接不是因为它不是
browser won't believe it and will abort
the connection it's not because it's not
在日志中，所以日志有点力量，因为
in the log
so the log sort of forces because
浏览器要求证书是日志，日志会强制所有证书
browsers require certificates being a
log the log forces all certificates to
在公开的地方可以由知道什么的监视器进行审核和检查
be public where they can be audited and
checked by monitors who know what the
适当的证书，我们的，所以一些显示器是由大公司经营的，
proper certificates our and so some
monitors are run by big companies and
公司知道自己的证书有些监视器由证书运行
companies know their own certificates
some monitors are run by certificate
代表客户的授权机构，然后再次是那些证书颁发机构
authorities on behalf of their customers
and again those certificate authorities
知道他们颁发给客户的证书是什么，他们至少可以
know what certificates they've issued to
their customers and they can at least
提醒客户，如果他们看到他们没有为以下其中一项颁发证书：
alert their customers if they see a
certificate they didn't issue for one of
他们的顾客名字我是另外还有一些完全第三方的显示器
their customers names I'm in addition
there's some totally third-party monitor
您让第三方监控器监控您的姓名，您的姓名和您的姓名的系统
systems where you give the third-party
monitor your names and yours and your
有效的证书，并检查您的姓名的预期证书
valid certificates and it checks for
expected certificates for your names
好的，这是整体方案，但很大程度上取决于浏览器
alright this is the overall scheme but
it depends very much on browsers seeing
监视器可以看到并记录的日志内容完全相同，但请记住，我们已经反对
the very same log contents that monitors
see and but remember we were up against
我们不确定是否可以信任此系统中的任何组件的问题
this problem that we're not sure that we
can trust any component in this system
所以确实我们发现此证书颁发机构中有些是恶意的
so indeed we found this certificate
authorities some of them are malicious
或拥有无法信任或草率的员工并且不遵守规则
or have employees who can't be trusted
or are sloppy and don't follow the rules
所以我们假设我们必须假设
so we're going to assume we have to
assume that the same will be true the
证书日志服务器，其中一些将是恶意的，其中一些可能
certificate log servers that some of
them will be malicious some of them may
与流氓证书颁发机构合谋并故意尝试
conspire with rogue certificate
authorities and intentionally try to
帮助他们签发伪造的证书有些证书可能草率的有些证书可能
help them issue bogus certificates some
of them may be sloppy some of them may
是合法的，但也许他们的一些员工或您支付的腐败费用
be legitimate but maybe some of their
employees or are corruptible you pay
他们是贿赂，所以我会在日志中做一些有趣的事情，删除或添加
them being a bribe so I'll do something
funny to the log delete something or add
东西，所以我们需要构建的是一个日志，即使该日志
something to it so what we need to build
is a log that even though the log
运营商可能不合作而不值得信赖，我们仍然可以确定或
operator may be not cooperating not
trustworthy we can still be sure or at
最不知道浏览器是否不是同一个日志竞赛者
least know if it's not the case that
browsers are seeing the same log contest
作为监视器，因此如果我们的浏览器使用了日志中的证书，
as monitors so if our browser uses a
certificate that was in the log the
监控拥有该名称的人最终会看到它，因此我们需要做的是
monitor who owns that name will
eventually see it so what we need to do
是我们需要构建一个仅追加的日志系统，以便它不会显示
is we need to build a log system that is
append-only so that it can't show a
证书到浏览器，然后在监视器看到它之前将其删除，因此仅附加
certificate to a browser then delete it
before monitors see it so append-only
没有叉，就意味着我们不需要日志
no Forks
in the sense that we don't want the log
系统基本上保留两个日志，其中一个显示两个浏览器，另一个显示
system to basically keep two logs one of
which it shows two browsers and one of
它显示了两个监视器，所以我们不需要叉子，我们需要不受信任的我们不能
which shows two monitors so we need no
Forks and we need untrusted we can't be
确保证书服务器正确无误，因此只需备份一下
sure that the certificate servers are
correct so just to back up a bit the
我们需要的日志系统的关键属性远远超出了日志服务器
critical properties we need for the log
system so larger than just a log servers
但是日志服务器的整个系统以及各种检查是我们必须
but the entire system of the log servers
plus the various checks is we have to
防止删除，因为我们只需要在日志后附加日志
prevent deletion that is we need the
logs to be append only because if a log
服务器可以从其日志中删除项目，然后它们可以有效地显示伪造
server could delete items out of its log
then they could effectively show a bogus
长期向浏览器索取者提供证书，也许在该日志中
certificate to a browser claimants in
the long and maybe in the log at that
浏览器使用它的时间，但也许此证书服务器可以删除
time the browser uses it but then maybe
this certificate server could delete
从其日志中获取该证书，以便在监控人员查看时
that certificate from its log so that by
the time the monitor's came to look at
伪造的证书不会在日志中，所以我们需要一个系统
the log the bogus certificate wouldn't
be there so we need to have a system
可以防止删除，或者至少可以检测是否发生删除，因此
that either prevents deletion or at
least detects if deletion occurred so
这就是系统只需要追加的意义，我们也有
that's the sense in which the system
needs to be append-only and we also have
为了防止所谓的“模棱两可”，我们必须防止Forks或
to prevent what's called equivocation or
not' we have to prevent Forks or
等同模棱两可
equivalently equivocation
所以您知道这可能是证书日志服务器可以
so you know it's
maybe the certificate log servers could
实现仅追加日志，但是如果实现了两个不同
be implementing append-only logs but if
it if it uh implemented two different
依靠唯一的日志并显示一个两个浏览器，并显示另一个仅附加的
depend the only logs and showed one two
browsers and show the other append-only
记录两个监视器，那么我们可能会处于一个位置，是的，您知道
log two monitors then we could be in a
position where yeah you know that the
浏览器显示的日志我们显示浏览器的包含虚假信息
browser that we showed the log we showed
the browser's contains the bogus
证书，但我们向监视器显示的日志不包含
certificate but the log we showed a
monitors doesn't doesn't contain the
伪造证书，因此我们必须排除所有人的模棱两可，
bogus certificate so we have to rule out
equivocation to all without trusting the
服务器，那么我们现在该如何做呢？
servers so how can we do this now we're
getting into the kind of details that
最后的作业是在谈论第一步是这个东西
the last of the assignments was talking
about the first step is this thing
叫做默克尔树，这有点像日志
called a Merkel tree and this is
something that's sort of that the log
服务器应该建立在日志的顶部，因此，想法是
servers are expected to build on top of
the log so the idea is that there's the
实际日志本身是一系列证书，您知道一个证书
actual log itself which is a sequence of
certificates you know certificate one
证书大概以证书的顺序
certificate to presumably in the order
that a certificate
证书要添加到系统中，我将要添加的前几百万
certificates to be added to the system
and the prime millions I'm just going to
假设现在有一对夫妇，事实证明，你知道我们不想拥有
assume there's a couple now it's gonna
turn out you know we don't want to have
浏览器必须下载整个日志，因此我们需要工具来使我们
the browser's have to download the whole
log and so we need tools to so that we
可以使日志记录系统基本上发送可信赖的摘要，或者
can allow the logging system to
basically send trustworthy summaries or
明确记录到浏览器中的内容，我将在其中进行讨论
unambiguous summaries of what's in the
log to the the browsers and I'll talk in
关于这些摘要的确切用途，但基本的
a bit about it exactly what those
summaries are used for but the basic
方案是日志服务器将使用加密哈希来进行哈希排序
scheme is that the log servers are gonna
use cryptographic hashes to sort of hash
完整的日志记录集可以产生一个
up the complete set of records that are
in the log can produce a single
密码散列这几天通常约为256位，因此
cryptographic hash which is typically
these days about 256 bits long so the
密码散列总结了日志的数量和方式
cryptographic hash summarizes the
countenance of the log and the way
这样做是因为基本上是成对的树结构
that's done is that the is as a
basically a tree structure of pairs over
哈希总是将零对级别的数字对哈希在一起，所以我
hash always hashing together pairs of
numbers at the zeroeth level so I'm
要为每个哈希写一个，每个日志条目都有一个哈希，所以我们
gonna write each for a hash each one of
the log entries has a hash so we're
在基本级别上，我们将拥有每个日志条目的哈希值
gonna have sort of at the base level we
have the hash of each log entry each
证书，然后我们将对等对象进行哈希处理，以便在下一级别
certificate and then we're going to hash
up peers so that the next level we're
会有一个哈希值，并与此关联，还有一个哈希值
gonna have a hash of this and
concatenated with this and a hash of
这与这两个哈希值串联在一起，然后在顶层
this concatenated with this these two
hashes and then at the top level sort of
我们正在做的是将这两个哈希串联在一起
we're we're overdoing is hashing these
two the concatenation of these two
哈希，这里的单个哈希是
hashes and this single hash here is a
完整日志的明确替代品之一是
unambiguous sort of stand-in for the
complete log one of the properties of
这些像sha-256这样的加密哈希值是不可能找到两个
these cryptographic hashes like sha-256
is that it's not feasible to find two
哈希函数的输入产生相同的输出，这意味着如果您
inputs to the hash function that produce
the same output and that means if you
告诉某人哈希函数的输出您只有一个输入
tell somebody the output of the hash
function there's only one input you're
曾经能够找到产生那个输出的东西，所以如果日志服务器
ever going to be able to find that
produce that output so if the log server
确实以这种方式散列其日志的内容，仅是这些日志的此顺序
does hash up in this way the contents of
its logs only this sequence of these log
记录将能够产生该哈希或有效地保证
records will ever be able to produce
that hash or guaranteed effectively that
日志服务器将无法找到其他产生日志的日志
the log server is not going to be able
to find some other log that produces the
与该日志条目序列相同的最终树哈希，所以这是
same final tree hash as this sequence of
log entries all right so this is the
默克尔树，这是一种树形哈希，用于总结整个日志
Merkel tree this is the sort of tree
hash that summarizes the entire log at
默克尔树的顶部实际上将其称为签名树头
the top of the Merkel tree there there's
will actually call it a signed tree head
因为实际上日志服务器将这个哈希值放在树的顶部
because in fact the log servers take
this hash this at the top of the tree
并使用其私钥对其进行签名，然后将其提供给浏览器和
and sign it with their private key and
give that to clients to browsers and
监视器以及他们已经签名的事实意味着他们不能
monitors and the fact that they've
signed it means that they they can't
后来拒绝了，实际上是他们，因此产生了它
disavow it later
that was really them and produced it so
那就是您知道能够捕获说谎的日志服务器，所以重点
that's you know just to be able to catch
lying lying log servers and so the point
这是一旦日志服务器揭示了一个特定的符号树头
here is that once a log server has
revealed a particular sign tree head to
浏览器或监视器对某些特定日志内容的承诺，因为
a browser or monitor its committed to
some specific log contents because it
将永远无法产生不同的日志内容来产生
won't be able to ever produce a
different log contents to produce the
相同的哈希，所以您的哈希实际上是作为一种承诺起作用的，所以
same hash so you hashes are really
function as kind of commitments okay so
这是日志的内容，但默克尔树看起来像是现在的特定日志
this is the with the log but the Merkel
tree looks like for a particular log now
今天的三读概述了如何
the third reading today sort of outlined
how to
法律如何将记录添加到日志中以获取任意数量的记录
and the law how to add records to the
log for arbitrary numbers of Records I'm
只是假设对数总是以2的倍数增长，这是
just going to assume that the log always
grows by factors of 2 which is
不切实际，但可以更容易地解释Naumann，因此这意味着
impractical but makes it easier to
explain Naumann so that means that as
证书颁发机构发送新证书以将日志添加到日志中
certificate authorities send in new
certificates to add to the log the log
服务器将等待，直到它拥有与旧记录一样多的新记录为止，并且
server will wait until it has as many
new records as it has old records and
然后产生另一个树头，这样做的方式是
then produce another tree head and the
way it does that is it's gonna in order
为了扩展日志，日志服务器将等待另外四个记录，并且
to extend the log the log servers going
to wait off as another four records and
然后像以前一样将它们成对散列，然后产生一个新的
then it's gonna hash them pairwise just
as before and then it'll produce a new
树头，这是这两个哈希的串联的哈希，并且
tree head that is the hash of the
concatenation of these two hashes and
这是新的扩展法则的新树头，因此意味着随着时间的推移
this is the new tree head for the new
expanded law and so that means as time
继续运行，并且日志服务器的日志越来越长，它会产生一些
goes on and a log server this log grows
longer and longer it produces sort of
越来越高的树头序列作为对数
higher and higher a sequence of higher
and higher tree heads as the logarithms
好的，这就是我们期望日志服务器维护的结构
okay so this is the structure that we're
expecting log servers to maintain of
谁知道他们实际在做什么，当然，如果他们是恶意的
course who knows what they're actually
doing especially if they're malicious
但是写了证书透明协议种类的协议
but the protocol the certificate
transparency protocol sort of is written
您知道好像日志服务器实际上正在执行此操作，那么该怎么办
you know as if the log server was was
actually doing this all right so what do
我们需要做，但要做的是Merkle树的要点是使用它们来强制记录
we need to do but do the point of this
Merkle trees is to use them to force log
服务器证明有关日志的某些事情，他们可以关于日志
servers to prove certain things about
the logs that they can about the log
他们正在维护，我们将要知道那些证明是什么
that they're maintaining we're going to
want to know what those those proofs
看起来第一种是所谓的包含证明
look like the first kind of
is what I'll call a proof of inclusion
这就是一个
and this is what a
当需要查找刚刚获得的证书时，NEADS
NEADS when it when it wants to find out
if a certificate that has just been
如果该证书确实在法律上，则由网络服务器提供
given by a web server if that
certificate is really in the law it's
要问证书，要问日志服务器，看这里是证书
gonna ask the certificate it's gonna ask
the log server look here's a certificate
你知道这是它在您的日志中，并且证书服务器将要发送
you know is it an is it in your log and
the certificate server is gonna send
不仅证明证书在日志中，而且还证明
back a proof of actually not just that
the certificate is in the log but
实际上它在日志中的位置以及浏览器中的位置
actually where it is what its position
is in the log and of course the browser
需要此证明，因为如果不在其中，则不想使用证书
wants this proof because it doesn't want
to use the certificate if it's not in
该日志，因为如果不是，那么我将无法看到监视器，并且有
否/-无法防止其证书被伪造，因此需要
no / - no protection against their
certificate being bogus and it needs to
作为证明，因为我们无力让此日志服务器成为恶意日志
be a proof because we we can't afford to
let this log server a malicious log
永远改变主意，我们不想接受日志服务器这个词，因为
forever change its mind we don't want to
take the log servers word for it because
那么他们可能是恶意日志服务器可能会说“是”，而该证明将
帮助我们了解您是否知道日志服务器是否说谎，这些证明将
help us catch it you know if a log
server does lie these proofs are gonna
帮助我们了解日志服务器撒谎并提供证据表明
help us catch the fact that the log
servers lied and produce evidence that
日志服务器是恶意的，从现在开始应该被忽略的是
the log server is malicious and should
be ignored from now on is that sort of
对日志服务器的最终制裁是浏览器实际上
the ultimate sanction against the log
servers is that the browser's actually
列出可接受的日志服务器，这些证明将是
have a list of acceptable log servers
and these proofs would be part of the
导致导致其中一台日志服务器从日志中取出的证据
evidence to cause one of the log servers
to be taken out of the log if it was
恶意好，所以我们需要一个证明，我们希望日志服务器产生一个证明
malicious okay so we need a proof we
want the log server to produce a proof
给定证书在其日志中，因此实际上第一步是
that a given certificate is in its log
so actually the first step is that the
浏览器向日志服务器询问当前的符号树头，因此
browser asks the log server for the
current sign tree head so what the
浏览器真正的问题是摘要日志中的此证书
browser's really asking is is this
certificate in the log that summarized
通过这个当前的符号树头和日志服务器可能会说谎
by this current by this sign tree head
and the log server may lie about the
浏览器向右询问符号树头，然后询问它当前的符号树头，然后
sign tree head right the browser asks it
for the current sign tree head and then
为了证明证书在日志中，日志服务器可能会说谎
for a proof that the certificate is in
the log the log server could lie about
符号树头带将解决这个问题，我们稍后会考虑，但对于
the sign tree headband will deal about
that we'll consider that later but for
现在，假设浏览器具有正确的符号树头，并且
now let's assume that the the browser
has the correct sign tree head and is
要求证明还可以，所以为了简单起见，我将解释如何执行此操作
demanding a proof okay so for simplicity
I'm just gonna explain how to do this
对于具有两个记录的日志，事实证明，将其扩展为具有
for a log with two records and it turns
out that extending that to a log with
与两个记录的其他更高次幂相对容易一些，所以
with other more higher power of two
records is relatively easy um so the
浏览器实际上有一个特殊的符号树头，让我们假设正确的日志
browser actually has a particular sign
tree head let's suppose the correct log
位于该标志树头下方的是特定于日志B的两个LM
that sits under that sign tree head is
the two LM in log a B for particular
证书a和B，这意味着正确
certificates a and B and that means that
the correct
默克尔树，因为它牢固地位于a和B的散列的底部，并且
Merkle tree for that it securely is at
the bottom as the hashes of a and B and
那么符号树的头部实际上就是一个与
then the sign tree head is actually the
hash of a hash of a concatenated with a
哈希将是这样，让我们​​假设这是证书的标志树头
hash would be so let's suppose this is
the sign tree head that the certificate
日志服务器实际上给了客户端的客户端当然不是
that the log server actually gave to the
client of course the client doesn't this
客户只知道这个值，这是最终的哈希值，实际上并不知道
client only knows this value this is
final hash value doesn't actually know
如果浏览器要求提供a的证明，则日志中的证明是什么
what is in the log the proof if the if
the browser asked for a proof that a is
在日志中，那么日志服务器可以返回的证明就是证明
in the log then the proof that the log
server can return is simply the proof
因为在日志中a是简单的eizan在日志中，而另一个的哈希
for a is a in the log is simply eizan in
the log and the hash of the other
日志中的元素，因此为零，b的哈希值
element in the log so zero and the hash
of b
而这足以让a服从自己，以对不起
and that is enough information for a to
convince itself that for sorry for the
客户说服自己真的处于零位，因为它可以
client to convince itself that a really
is at position zero because it can take
它知道证书有兴趣，可以将其哈希一部分证明是
it knows the certificate is interested
in it can hash it part of the proof was
该最低级别哈希中另一个元素的哈希，以便浏览器可以
the hash of the other element in this
lowest level hash so the browser can
现在知道H a和HB，您可以将它们哈希在一起，可以执行此哈希，并且
that now knows H a and H B you can hash
them together can execute this hash and
查看结果是否与发生的正弦树头相同，以及是否
see if the result is the same as the
sine tree head that it happens and if it
则表示证书日志实际上产生了有效的证明
is then that means that the certificate
log is actually produce a valid proof
证书a位于位置B，很抱歉，它的位置为零
that certificate a is at position B
that's a sorry it's a position zero in
该符号树头总结的日志，事实证明，
the log summarized by this sign tree
head and it turns out that in larger
较大的日志，如果您需要查找，则知道是否需要证明
larger logs you know if you're looking
for if you need a proof that a is really
在这里，您需要做的是每个散列的另一个分支的哈希序列
here all you need is the sequence of
hashes of the other branch of each hash
直到您拥有的符号树头，如果在
up to the sign tree head that you have
so in a for element log if you if you
需要证明a位置为零，您需要此哈希单位，然后需要
need a proof that a is position zero you
need this hash units then you need this
哈希，如果锁更大，您知道八个元素，那么您也需要这个
hash and if the lock is bigger you know
eight elements then you also need this
散列，假设您已经击中了签名树，那么您可以将元素
hash assuming that you have the signed
tree hit so you can take the element you
知道并将其与其他哈希值一起哈希，看看它是否等于
know and hash it together with each of
these other hashes see if it's equal to
标志树的头还好，所以如果浏览器问的是假设浏览器
the sign tree head okay so if the
browser asks is supposing the browser
询问X是否在位置0的日志中X不在日志中，所以
asks whether X is in the log at position
zero well X isn't in the log right so
希望日志服务器没有简单的方法来产生X的证明
hopefully there's no easy way for the
log server to produce the proof that X
位于日志位置零，但假设日志服务器想要说谎并且
is in the log in position zero but
suppose the log servers wants to lie and
它的位置已经暴露了一个用于日志的符号树头
it's in the position where it already
exposed a sign tree head for log that
包含A，然后B浏览器不知道是A，B不知道其中包含什么
contain a and then B browser doesn't
know was a and B doesn't know what's in
日志和日志服务器想要欺骗客户端进入浏览器
the log and the log server wants to
trick the client into the browser into
认为它真的在零位，结果是
thinking that it's really
at position zero well it turns out that
为此，证书服务器必须为此小日志
in order to do that the for this small
log the certificate server has to
产生一些为什么它需要找到一个为什么，如果需要它是一个哈希
produce for some why it needs to find a
why that if it takes it's hash one
与X串联在一起，所以这就是它等于符号树
concatenated with X you know so this is
that's that it's equal to the sign tree
向右走，因为我们假设客户已经必须签署
head right because the client we're
assuming the client already has to sign
树头，我们需要在此处找到一些数字，将其与
tree head we need to find a some number
here that when hashed together with the
客户询问产生相同符号树的X哈希打得很好
hash of X that the clients asking about
produces that same sign tree hit well we
知道符号树的头或假设是分配给它的树
know the sign tree head or the
assumption is assigned tree it was
实际上是为了其他一些日志，因为我们正在尝试排除
actually for some other log right
because we're trying to rule out the
日志服务器可以给您一个日志的树头的可能性，但是
possibility that the log server can give
you a sign tree head for one log but
使您确信该日志中还存在其他内容，因此该符号
that convince you that something else is
in that log that's not there so the sign
真正的树是由记录的散列产生的
tree had really was produced by from the
hashes of the records that really were
在日志中，现在我们需要，因为您知道X绝对不同于a
in the log and now we need and since you
know X is definitely different from a
这意味着X的哈希与a的哈希不同，这意味着
that means the hash of X is different
from the hash of a and that means that
日志服务器需要为哈希函数找到两个不同的输入
the log server needs to find two
different inputs to the hash function
产生了相同的输出，并且该假设被普遍认为是正确的
that produced the same output and the
Assumption widely believed to be true
出于实际目的，这对于加密散列是不可能的
for practical purposes is that that's
not possible for cryptographic hashes
因此，通过对一个日志进行哈希运算来生成分号树头
therefore the cent sign tree head was
produced by hashing up one log that it
将找不到这些其他类型的哈希值
will not be possible to find these sort
of other hash values that would be
需要提供证明，证明其他一些元素不在日志中
required to produce a proof that some
other element was in the log that wasn't
真的对此有任何疑问
really there
any questions about this about anything
[音乐]有趣的是
[Music]
interesting a nice thing about this is
证明就是证明只是由其他散列组成
that the proofs are the proofs consist
of just the sort of other hashes on the
如果有n个证书，则上升到根目录，只有其他
way up to the root if there's n
certificates there's only log in other
哈希值，因此证明特别合理，其中很多
hashes and so the proofs are reasonably
concise in particular that are much much
小于完整日志，并且因为您知道每个需要连接的浏览器
smaller than the full log and since you
know every browser that needs to connect
到一个网站，他需要这些证明之一，如果它们很小的话，那很好
to a website he's going to need one of
these proofs it's good if they're small
好吧，这是整个讨论，是假设符号树具有
okay well this was whole discussion was
assuming that the sign tree had the
主题
theum
或具有正确的符号树头（如果没有），但没有立即的原因
or had was the correct sign tree head if
the but no there's no immediate reason
相信日志服务器会给出如果日志是恶意的
to believe that the log server would
have given if the logs are is malicious
它想欺骗客户，你知道为什么会给客户正确的答案
and it wants to trick a client you know
why would it give the client the correct
看到标志树头为什么不给它，只是我给标志树头给
see sign tree head why doesn't it give
it just me giving the sign tree head for
它想要欺骗客户端使用的虚假日志，所以我们必须
the bogus log that it wants to trick the
client into using so we have to be
准备好日志服务器已经准备好的可能性
prepared for the possibility that the
log server has cooked up I just
与浏览器完全不同的日志，与其他人的日志不同
completely different log for the browser
that's not like anybody else's log and
它只包含恶意日志服务器想要的伪造证书
it just contains the bogus certificates
that a malicious log server wants to
诱使这个客户相信，所以我们该怎么做呢？
trick this client into believing so what
do we do about that well it turns out
至少在一开始就完全有可能
that this is at least in the first
instance this is totally possible
你知道通常会发生什么
you know usually what's gonna happen
usually the way this will play out is
我们将拥有一些浏览器，您会知道看到正确的日志，直到一些
that we'd have some browser that was you
know seeing the correct logs until some
当某人想要攻击它的时间点，并且您知道您想要
point in time when when somebody wanted
to attack it and you know you want the
浏览器学生可以使用它通常看到的所有网站
browser student be able to use all the
websites that it's ordinarily seeing
加上日志服务器所需的带有伪证书的其他日志
plus a sort of different log with bogus
certificates that the log server wants
欺骗那个客户只是受害者的浏览器来使用，所以现在这是
to trick just that client just that
victim browser into using so now this is
叉子攻击或更广泛的模棱两可，以及人们为什么
a fork fork attack or more broadly
equivocation and the reason why people
称这种攻击为分叉攻击是，如果我们从不
call this kind of attack
a fork attack is that if we just never
如果我们只考虑日志通常是日志，请介意默克尔树一会儿
mind the Merkel tree for a moment if we
just consider the log usually the log
已经知道您有数百万个证书，每个人都可以看到
already has you know millions of
certificates in it and everybody's seen
日志的开始部分，然后在某个时间点我们想攻击我们
the beginning part of the log then at
some point in time we want to attack we
想要说服我们的受害者使用一些伪造的证书B，但我们不想
want to persuade our victim to use some
bogus certificate B but we don't want to
向其他人展示B当然不在显示器上，所以我们要做饭
show B to anybody else certainly not to
the monitor so we're gonna sort of cook
在其他日志中继续照常进行，并包含新的提交
up this other log the sort of continues
as usual and contains new submissions
但绝对不包含伪造的证书B，您知道这是什么
but definitely doesn't contain the bogus
certificate B and you know what this
看起来像是一个叉子，因为同时显示了监视器的主日志类型
looks like is a fork because both the
sort of main log that monitors are shown
有点不合时宜，然后我们正在制作这个vlog，特别是
is kind of off on one fork and then this
vlog we're cooking up especially to
欺骗受害者是不同的叉子，这是恶意的构造
trick a victim is a different fork this
is the construction that the malicious
如果它想欺骗浏览器使用
log server would have to produce if it
wants to trick a browser into using a
伪造的证书，再次这些都是可能的，可以在
bogus certificate and again these are
possible it's possible to do this at
至少短暂地与证书颁发机构一起筛选合适的透明度
least briefly in with certificate
authority the sift a fit transparency
幸运的是，这还不是故事的结局，并且证书颁发机构还包含
luckily though is not the end of the
story and certificate authority contains
一些使它变得更困难的工具，所以基本方案
some tools that allow it to make Forks
much more difficult so the basic scheme
是不是这是证书颁发机构预期的方式
is that this isn't this is the way the
certificate authority sort of intended
使所有证书透明化都可以正常工作，但并不完全
to work all certificate transparency is
intended to work but doesn't quite
这里发生的是显示器和人员都没有
what's going on here is that the the the
monitors and people are not being
被攻击或会看到一棵标志树，特别是标志树的头，比如说
attacked or gonna see a a sign tree
particular sign tree head let's say
我们碰到的一门科学当然会随着日志的扩展和受害人而改变
science we hit one of course is gonna
change as the log extends and the victim
我们知道必须看到其他一些符号树的头部，因为这是一个符号树命中
we know must see some other sign tree
head because this is a signed tree hit
散列于此
that is hashed over this
保证与标志树头不同的证书，这是
certificates guaranteed to be different
from the sign tree heads this is the
如果只有浏览器和监视器可以，民兵服务将显示两个监视器
militia service showing two monitors
if only the browsers and monitors could
比较笔记，他们可能会立即意识到他们看到了不同
compare notes they would maybe instantly
realize that they were seeing different
树木和它所需要的只是比较您是否知道我们是否正确地玩牌
trees and all it takes is comparing you
know if we play our cards right all it
需要比较的是从日志服务器获得的符号树到
takes is comparing the sign tree had its
they've gotten from the log server to
意识到等等，我们现在看到的是不同的日志
realize wait a minute we're seeing
different logs now something's terribly
错误的，所以我们需要做的关键事情是拥有不同的
wrong so the critical thing we need to
do is have have the different
系统的参与者能够比较标志树的头部和
participants in the system be able to
compare sign tree heads and the
证书透明性对此所谓的八卦及其使用方式做了规定
certificate transparency has a provision
for this called gossip and the way it's
旨在使浏览器运行良好，但细节并不重要，但重要的是
intended to works that browsers well the
details don't really matter but what it
真正的意义在于，所有参与者都将最近的
really amounts to is that all the
participants sort of drop off the recent
他们看到了一个大水池，他们都检查试图把树头签下，
sign tree heads they've seen into a big
pool that they all inspect to try to
找出是否有不一致的标志树头清楚地表明
figure out if there's inconsistent sign
tree heads that clearly indicate
有不同的日志，所以我们将八卦，这实际上意味着
divergent logs that have for it so we're
going to gossip which really means
交换
exchange
我正在签名树桩，并进行比较，结果表明当前的证书
I'm sign tree heads and compare it turns
out that current certificate
透明度实现不这样做，但他们应该这样做，并且会
transparency implementations don't do
this but they ought to and they'll
弄清楚一点好吧，所以给出了问题
figure it out at some point
all right okay so the question is given
签署树头，我们如何确定他们是否证明日志已被记录
to sign tree heads how do we decide if
they're evidence that the log has been
分叉的原因是，即使没有将日志分叉为
forked the thing that makes this hard is
that even if a log hasn't been forked as
这取决于新的符号树头是否会成为最新，所以您可能知道
it's depended to new sign tree heads
will become current so you know maybe
标志树的头一个是合法的，所以他此时有一个博客
sign tree head one was the legitimate so
he had a vlog at this point of then some
添加了更多证书，并且符号树的头部3成为了正确的头部
more certificates are added and sign
tree head 3 becomes the correct head of
法律，然后签名树头等等，所以这八卦到底是什么
the law and then signed tree head for
etc so really what this gossip
比较最少要做的是区分一个标志树头是
comparison least to do is distinguish
situations where one sign tree head is
真正描述了一个日志的前缀，它是另一个描述的日志的前缀
really describes a prefix a log that's a
prefix of the log described by another
标志树的头部，因为这是您拥有的合法情况
sign tree head because this is the
legitimate situation where you have the
这两个标志树头有两个不同，但第二个确实有
two these two sign tree heads are
different but the second one really does
包含第一个，我们想将其与两个有符号树区分开来
subsume the first one we want to
distinguish that from two signed tree as
不同之处在于，两者都没有描述作为前缀的日志
that are different where neither
describes a log that's a prefix of the
另一个人的日志将这两种情况分开，将这种情况分开
other one's log one tell these two cases
apart this telling that situation apart
一致性证明的目的是日志或默克尔一致性证明，
is the purpose of the consistency proof
the log or Merkel consistency proof that
谈论阅读，所以这是
the reading is talked about so this is
the
一致性证明
la consistency proof
您
you
所以这里的游戏是让我们给树头H 1和H 2签名，
so the game here is that we're given to
sign tree heads H 1 and H 2 and we're
问的是h 1s日志前缀，实际上不是这些-这些是哈希，所以
asking is h 1s log prefix really it's
not these are - these are hashes so it's
真正询问散列所代表的日志，您知道我们在
really asking about the log that the
hashes represent and you know we're
希望答案为是，如果答案为否，则意味着日志
hoping the answer is yes and if the
answer's no that means that the log
服务器Fork Dustin正在某一方或另一方隐藏东西，好吧
servers Fork Dustin is hiding something
from one party or the other okay well it
就像我们之前提到的那样，那个默克尔树作为对数
turns out that um as we as I mentioned
before the as the Merkel tree as the log
默克尔树也长了，我们看到的是一系列的迹象
grows the Merkel tree also grows and
what we see is a sequence of signs of
每棵树的头顶为原木的两倍，每棵树的头顶为左
tree heads each one as a log doubles in
size each one has its as its left thing
让我画一下这个哈希函数的实际哈希函数是将两个
let me draw in the actual hash functions
of this hash function is hashing up two
事情这个哈希函数的结果
things the result of this hash function
是下一个符号树头的输入之一，此哈希的结果
is one of the inputs to the next sign
tree head the result of this hash
函数是下一个符号树头的输入之一，我知道我们知道了
function is one of the inputs to the
next sign tree head I know we get this
生命之树的种类签树头好吧，如果需要，我需要签树头
kind of tree of life sign tree heads all
right and I need to sign tree heads if
它们是合法的，您知道每个log是否为H 2的前缀
they're legitimate you know if each one
is log is a prefix of H 2 that means
也许这个人的H 1和这个人的H 2他们会拥有这个
that maybe this one's H 1 and this one's
H 2 and they're gonna have this
你知道的关系事物如果每个人都是一块H 2，那么他们一定有
relationship thing you know if each one
is a piece of H 2 then they must have
这种关系是通过对每个2进行散列来产生每个2
this relationship where each 2 was
produced by taking each one hashing it
与其他东西，也许与其他东西哈希，直到我们得到
with some other thing and maybe hashing
that with some other thing until we get
到找到H 2的地步，意思是如果浏览器或监视器
to the point where we find H 2 and with
means is that if a browser or monitor
向日志服务器挑战日志，以证明每个人的日志确实是前缀
challenges a log a log server to prove
that each one's log is really a prefix
h2s log日志服务器必须生成的是其他
of h2s log what the log server has to
produce is this sequence of other the
从h1到h2的途中，每个Hat标志树的头哈希值的另一侧，
other side of each of the Hat sign tree
head hashes on the way from h1 to h2 and
这就是证明，然后再次您知道这让人想起
this is the proof and then again you
know this is reminiscent of the
包含证明然后检查证明，您需要将每个哈希与
inclusion proofs then to check the proof
you need to take each one hash it with
您知道的第一件事与第二件事
the first other thing you know hash that
along with the second other things that
您到达其中的最后一个，并且最好等于h2
you get to the last one of these and
that had better be equal to h2 if it is
证明h2是每个后缀的后缀，否则日志服务器显然
it's a proof that h2 is a suffix of each
one otherwise the log servers evidently
试图分叉你一次又一次，你知道的基础是，没有别的
tried to fork you and again you know the
basis of this is that there's no other
你知道h2确实不是因为假设h1不是h2的前缀，所以不可能
you know h2 really isn't as supposing h1
isn't a prefix of h2 there's no way that
嗯，因为h2是根据与h1不同的实际日志创建的，所以没有
uh since h2 was created from some actual
log that's not the same as h1 there's no
日志服务器可以准备导致这些值的方法
way that the log server could cook up
these values that are required to cause
这种将h1等于H到H的重复哈希的哈希确实包含
the hashes this sort of repeated hash of
h1 to equal H to H do really encompass
这表明加密哈希确实阻止您绑定到其他
ooming that the cryptographic hash does
prevent you from binding to different
产生相同输出的输入
inputs that produce the same out
好吧，所以这是日志一致性证明，所以这个问题
alright ok so this is the log
consistency proof okay so the question
通常是向日志服务器发起挑战的人，因此我将在
is who usually challenges the log server
so I'll actually talk about that in a
分钟，但事实证明，无论是浏览器还是监视器
minute but it turns out that um both
browsers and monitors
Luke浏览器和监视器很好地挑战了您的日志服务器
well Luke browsers and monitors
challenge the log server you it's
实际上，通常浏览器会挑战日志服务器
actually usually the browser's
challenging the log server that's the
最重要的事情，但是有两个时间点需要
most important thing but there's two
points in time at which you need to
挑战日志服务器以提供这些证明，我将讨论
challenge the log server to produce
these proofs and I'll talk about both of
他们没事，实际上，所以第一点在哪一点
them all right okay actually so the
first place at which one point at which
这些证据用于八卦，正如我概述的八卦一样，
these proofs are used as for gossip as
part of gossip as I outlined and the the
用于八卦的方案是浏览器会定期与
scheme that's intended for gossip is
that browsers will periodically talk to
一些中央存储库的一些中央存储库，只是贡献
some central repository of some set of
central repositories and just contribute
到标志树头池，标志树命中了最近从日志中看到的树
to a pool of sign tree heads the sign
tree hits the recently seen from the log
服务器和浏览器也定期提取随机元素
server and the browsers were also
periodically pull out random elements of
其他浏览器仅看到Brandon的树头，他们将其拔出
sign tree heads that other browsers have
seen just Brandon they pulled them out
池中的多个池，这些池将由这些池运行
of the pool and it'll be multiple of
these collects these pools run by
不同的人，所以如果其中一个人在作弊，那将证明
different people so that if one of them
is cheating that will be proof against
然后，浏览器将针对任何随机符号树具有的内容
that and then the browser will for
whatever just any random sign tree has
苹果从池中出来，它将要求日志服务器生成日志
it apples out of the pool it will ask
the log server to produce the logs
一对标志树头的持久性证明，你知道是否没人
insistency proof for that pair of sign
tree heads and you know if nobody's
作弊设计，日志服务器应该总是很容易产生您所知道的
cheating design it should always be easy
for the log server to produce you know
任何需要的一致性证明，但如果有人认为
any consistency proof that's demanded of
it but if it's for somebody suppose it
日志服务器是给某人的，给他们一个标志树
the log server is for somebody and given
them a sign tree had this really
描述一个完全不同的日志，甚至描述一个长时间的差异
describes a totally different log or
even a long the difference in one
其他人最终看到的日志中的元素
element from the logs that everybody
else is seeing eventually that browser
将有助于标志树头到池中的八卦池，然后
will contribute that's that sign tree
head to the pool the gossip pool then
最终，我们将其他人从招牌托盘中拉出
eventually somebody else
we'll pull that sign tray head out of
游泳池并要求提供证据，因为您知道其他一些标志树有
the pool and ask for a proof for you
know some other sign tree had that
大概是在另一个Fork上，那么日志服务器将无法
presumably is on a different Fork and
then the log server will not be able to
出示证明，我是因为他们是自科学家签署的，还是由
produce the proof and I'm since they're
signed since the scientist or signed by
绝对证明该日志服务器已分叉了两个日志服务器
the log server that's just absolute
proof that the log server has forked two
的客户大概有意向其中一个客户透露伪造证书
of its clients presumably with intent
reveal a bogus certificate to one of
将它们隐藏起来，但是实际上在另一个地方
them and hide it from the other okay but
there's actually another place where it
事实证明，您需要这些一致性，不仅在八卦期间，而且在
turns out you need the these consistency
proves not just during gossip but
实际上也在浏览器的常规操作过程中，所以
actually also during the ordinary
operation of the browsers so the the
困难是假设您知道假设浏览器是
difficulty is that suppose you know
suppose the browser is it's kind of
看到一致的日志版本与其他所有人相同，但随后是日志
seeing consistent version of the log is
the same as everybody else but then log
服务器想要欺骗它使用此伪造的证书，因此日志服务器
server wants to trick it into using this
bogus certificate so the log server
向其发送签名的树，您知道该签名的树与
sends it a signed tree you know makes
signed RIA that's different from
其他人都指的是您知道包含此错误的恶意日志
everybody else that refers to a you know
malicious log that contains this bad
证书首选视频，因为它不希望其他人注意到
certificate preferred video since it
doesn't want other people to notice
当然不希望您知道监视器知道您已经做饭了
certainly doesn't want you know the
monitors to notice you know cooks up
这是其他所有人都可以看到的其他日志，所以现在您
this other log that is what everybody
else is seeing all right so now the you
知道浏览器检查并看到您知道我要求提供包含证明，并且
know the browser checks and sees you
know I asked for inclusion proof and the
包含，日志服务器将能够产生包含证明，因为
inclusion that log server will be able
to produce the inclusion proof because
这个标志树有浏览器确实确实引用了这个错误的日志
this sign tree had that the browser has
really does refer to this bad log the
浏览器将继续使用此虚假证书，并可能被欺骗并
browser will go ahead and use this bogus
certificate and maybe get tricked and
泄露用户密码，您知道谁知道，但是取决于
give away the user's password
you know who knows what but depending on
其他浏览器的详细信息正常工作，我们将在下次浏览器中承担风险
the details of other browsers work we're
at risk of the next time the browser
它没有意识到有什么地方出了问题与日志服务器对话
which it doesn't realize anything's gone
wrong talks to the log server the log
然后，服务器可能会说您知道有一个新日志，上面有一堆新东西
server might then say you know there's a
new log with a bunch of new stuff on it
这是当前日志的符号树为什么不切换
and here is the sign tree
of the current log why don't you switch
我可以将其用作您的标志树命中率，所以现在就让它发生
my to use that as your sign tree hit and
so now if that were allowed to happen
那么浏览器现在将完全失去任何证据
then the browser's now would completely
lost the evidence that anything went
错误的，因为现在浏览器正在使用其他所有人使用的相同树
wrong because now the browser is using
the same trees everybody else no it's
将把这个标志树的头贡献到八卦池中
going to contribute this sign tree head
to the gossip pool it's all gonna look
好，我们有这种短暂的邪恶树，那是被揭露的邪恶日志
good and we had this sort of brief evil
tree that was evil log that was revealed
邪恶的日志叉，但是如果浏览器愿意接受新的符号树头
evil log Fork but if the browser's are
willing to accept a new sign tree head
那么我们基本上可以让浏览器忘掉，所以我们想要的是
then we can basically have the browser
forget about so we want what we want is
这是我们想要的，如果浏览器如果日志服务显示特定日志
this what we want is for if a browser if
the log service shows a particular log
浏览器，他们无法将浏览器诱骗到的浏览器
to the browser that the browser that
they can't trick the browser into
从该日志中切换，我们希望能够执行该日志
switching away from that log that is
that we want to be able to enforce that
浏览器只会看到已经看到的严格的日志扩展名，并且
the browser sees only strict extensions
to the log that it's seen already and
不仅会切换到与该日志不兼容的日志，
doesn't simply get switched to a log
that is not compatible with the log the
在我们所寻找的属性之前看到的浏览器实际上是
browser seen before it's the property
that we're looking for it's actually
要求保持一致，任何前两个是，如果浏览器
called for consistency and with any
first two is that if the browser's been
与其他人分叉到另一个叉子上，那么他们必须留在那个叉子上
forked onto a different fork from other
people then they must stay on that fork
在其中它永远都不能切换到主叉子，其原因
in it it should never be able to switch
to the main fork and the reason for that
是我们要保存吗，您需要保存这个坏兆头和它的
is we want to preserve you need to
preserve this bad sign tree head and its
后继者，以便当浏览器参与八卦协议时
successors so that when the browser
participates in the gossip protocol it's
贡献没有其他人拥有且无法证明是的标志树头
contributing sign tree heads that nobody
else has and that cannot be proved to be
使用日志一致性证明可以兼容，那么我们如何实现
compatible using the log consistency
proof okay so how do we achieve for
一致性很好，使用我们现在每次使用的工具实际上都很容易
consistency well um it's actually easy
with the tools we have now every time
日志服务器告诉浏览器哦，这是一个更长的日志的新符号树头
the log server tells a browser oh here's
a new sign tree head for a longer log
浏览器将要求直到
the browser will require the will not
accept the new sign tree head until the
日志服务器已产生了日志一致性证明，即新的符号树
log server has has produced a log
consistency proof that the new sign tree
头描述了旧符号树的后缀，即旧日志的日志
head describes a suffix of the old sign
tree that is that the log of the old
符号树的前缀是新符号树的日志，当然如果有日志
sign tree has a prefix of the log of the
new sign tree and of course if a log
服务器与浏览器一样分叉，并且将浏览器保持在同一分叉上
server is as forked the browser and it's
keeping the browser on that same Fork it
可以产生证明，但您当然知道它正在更深入地挖掘自己的坟墓
can produce the proofs but of course you
know it's digging its grave even deeper
因为我正在生产越来越多的符号树头
because I'm as producing more and more
sign tree heads for a which will
最终被八卦协议所捕获，而如果博客服务器
eventually be caught by the gossip
protocol whereas if the blog server
尝试使浏览器切换到描述相同符号的树头
tries to cause the browser to switch to
a sign tree head that describes the same
记录其他人已经看到浏览器将要求一致性证明的日志
log everybody else has been seeing the
browser will demand a consistency proof
并且日志服务器将无法生成该日志，因为它会记录日志
and the log server will not be able to
produce it because deed the log
第一个符号树头描述的日志不是该日志描述的日志的前缀
described by the first sign tree head is
not a prefix of the log described by the
第二个标志树
second sign tree
好吧好吧，所以这些日志一致性证明为系统提供了
okay okay so the system these these log
consistency proofs provide for
一致性，一致性和闲聊以及需要此日志的情况
consistency and for consistency plus
gossiping and that requiring this log
一致性证明了通过闲聊发现的科学
consistency proves for the science found
by gossiping
我是他们两个人一起使所有参与者或
I'm the two of them together make it
likely that all the participants or
看到相同的日志，如果他们没有看到相同的日志，他们将能够
seeing the same log and that if they're
not seeing the same log they'll be able
通过日志一致性证明的失败来检测该事实
to detect that fact by the failure of a
log consistency proof
任何问题
any questions
好的，那么有多少个日志服务是一个很大的问题
okay so that how many log service are
there that is a great question
所以我将系统描述为好像只有一台日志服务器
so I describe the system as if there was
just one log server it turns out in the
在实际系统中，至少有很多日志服务器，因此这是一个已部署的
real system there's lots of log servers
at least dozens so this is a deployed
您可以在其中编程的系统实际上是由Chrome使用的，我认为
system which you can programmed in that
is actually used by Chrome and I think
Safari至少有几十个这样的日志服务器，当有证书时
Safari there are at least dozens of
these log servers and when certificate
chrome实际要求证书颁发机构提交所有证书
and certificate authorities are actually
required by chrome to submit all their
证书到日志服务器到多个日志服务器的不同
certificates to the to the log servers
to multiple log servers the different
日志服务器实际上并不保留相同的日志，约定是
log servers don't actually keep
identical logs the convention is that a
证书颁发机构将提交新证书，以节省您的时间。
certificate authority will submit a new
certificate to save you know a couple
可能是五个不同的日志服务器，实际上在证书信息中
maybe five different log servers and
actually in the certificate information
网站告诉您的浏览器，其中包括日志服务器的身份
that a website tells your browser it
includes the identities of log servers
证书所在的证书透明度日志服务器的数量
of the certificate transparency log
servers that have the certificate in
他们的日志，以便您的浏览器知道与哪些日志服务器进行通信以及原因
their log so your browser knows which
log servers to talk to and the reason
为什么其中不止一个原因当然是其中一些可能会变坏
why there's more than one of them is of
course some of them may go bad some of
他们可能被证明是恶意软件或倒闭，或者谁知道该怎么办
them may turn out to be malicious or go
out of business or who knows what and in
那样的话，你仍然希望有更多的东西可以依靠
that case you still want to have a
couple more to fall back on they don't
必须相同，因为只要证书在
have to be identical because they don't
as long as the certificate is in at
据任何人所知，至少有一个日志是值得信赖的
least one log that's you know as far as
anybody knows is trustworthy that's
足够，因为您知道这里的问题
sufficient because you know the issue
here
日志中确实包含证书的事实并不一定，因为
not really necessarily the fact that the
log had the certificate in it because
这并不能证明证书是好的，我们正在寻找的只是日志
that's not proof that the certificate is
good all we're looking for is log
不分叉使用它们的监视器和浏览器的服务器，因此
servers that aren't forking the monitors
and browsers that use them so it's
足够一个证书甚至放在不分叉的单个日志服务器中
enough for a certificate to be in even a
single log server that's not forking
人们，因为然后保证监视器可以看到它，因为
people because then the monitors are
guaranteed to see it because the
监视器检查所有日志服务器，以便即使出现伪造的证书也不会显示
monitors check all the log servers so if
a bogus certificate shows up even even a
监视器最终将注意到单个日志服务器，因为所有
single log server the monitors will
eventually notice because all the
监视器查看浏览器愿意接受的所有日志服务器
monitors look at all the log servers
that the browsers are willing to accept
好的，另一个问题是什么阻止日志服务器宕机和发出
all right another question what prevents
a log server from going down and issuing
伪造的证书在被抓住之前您实际上一无所知
bogus certificates before they get
caught you know nothing actually if
您愿意，这肯定是系统的缺陷，至少对于
you're willing to that's definitely a
defect in the system that at least for a
当您可以恶意造假日志服务器时
while you can
malicious log server contributing bogus
证书，因此，如果您拥有的证书颁发机构已成为
certificates so if you have a
certificate authority that's become
恶意的，并且发出伪造的证书，它们看上去很正确，但是
malicious and this issuing bogus
certificates they look correct but
他们是伪造的，还有一个日志服务器，那么愿意为他们服务
they're bogus and a log server then that
that's willing to serve these it's
愿意将这些证书放在日志中，当然它们都在
willing to put these certificates in the
log and of course they all are then at
至少有一段时间，浏览器会愿意使用它们，尽管
least for a while browsers will be
willing to use them the thing is though
那你知道他们会被抓住的，这就是系统的意图
that the you know they will be caught
and this is the system is its intent is
改善神父的状况或建立透明度制度，如果
to improve the situation in the priests
or to make a transparency system if
有人发放伪造的证书，浏览器被欺骗
somebody was issuing bogus certificates
and browsers were being tricked into
使用它们，您可能永远不会在证书透明性世界中发现
using them you might never find out ever
in the certificate transparency world
您可能不会立即发现，因此有些人可能会使用它们，但是随后
you may not find out right away and so
some some people may use them but then
您很快就会知道几天或显示器将开始的工作
relatively quickly you know a few days
or something the monitors will start to
请注意，日志中有错误的证书，有人会去跟踪
notice that there's bad certificates in
the logs and somebody will go and track
找出并找出谁是恶意的或谁在犯错误
it down and figure out who is malicious
or who is making mistakes
是的，所以我想一个证书，一个证书透明度法可以
yeah so I guess a certificate a
certificate transparency law could
拒绝跟显示器说话，是的，我不确定我是否最终认为
refuse to talk to the monitors yeah I'm
not sure I think ultimately the if you
知道我们现在正在步入非技术领域，您知道该怎么做
know we're now treading into a kind of
non-technical region you know what to do
如果有证据表明出了问题，这实际上是很难的
if there's evidence that something's
gone wrong this is actually quite hard
因为很多时候甚至是虚假的东西都会出问题
because much of the time is something
seems to go wrong even bogus
证书经常是一个人犯错的原因，这是一个
certificates often often the reason it's
just somebody made a mistake it was a
您知道有人吹嘘的合法错误，但这不是恶意的证据
legitimate mistake you know somebody
blew it and it's not evidence of malice
只是有人犯了一个错误，我想如果监视器是
is just that somebody made a mistake I
think what would happen if a monitor was
几乎以任何方式表现不佳，例如在执行过程中不回答请求
misbehaving in almost any way like not
answering requests if it was doing
人们总是注意到并要求他们整形或将其从中取出
consistently people notice and either
ask them to shape up or take them out of
列表停止使用它们的浏览器供应商
the list
stop using them the browser vendors
过一会儿，它将把她从可接受的日志服务器列表中注销
would take that logs her out of a list
of acceptable log servers after a while
但是，是的，有一个灰色的不良行为区域，对于
but yeah there's like a gray area of bad
behavior that's not bad enough to the
保证从我认为是日志服务器的可接受列表中删除
warrant being taken out of the
acceptable list I think of a log server
被发现工作正常，问题是如果找到了日志服务器该怎么办
has been found to work the question is
what if the log server has been found
在发生什么事情之前，我想我认为将会发生的事情是
before what happens then I think I think
what would happen is the people who were
运行，您知道浏览器供应商将与日志服务器交谈的人员，以及
run you know the people who the browser
vendors would talk to the log server and
向他们询问运行日志服务器的人员，并询问他们发生了什么事以及是否
ask them the people running the log
server and ask them what happened and if
他们提出了令人信服的解释，他们没有做出
错误，您知道哪个也许他们不能，也许我不知道他们他们
mistake you know which maybe they
couldn't maybe I don't know they their
机器崩溃，丢失了他们的日志的一部分，他们重新启动，您知道从
日志的前缀，如果出现错误，则开始增加其他日志
a prefix of the log and start growing a
different log if it seems like a mistake
诚实的错误那么这是一个错误，但是如果日志服务器
honest mistake then well it was a
mistake but if it if the log server
运营商无法提供令人信服的解释，然后我
operators can't provide a convincing
explanation of what happened then I
认为浏览器供应商只会将它们从可接受的列表中删除
think the browser vendors would just
delete them from the list of acceptable
klog服务器可以，但是您知道这些是
klog servers okay but these are you know
these are sort of problems with the
系统，因为您可以知道谁拥有名称或
system because you can you know the
definitions of like who owns a name or
可以接受，但是您知道服务器停机还是可以的
what acceptable but you know whether
it's okay for your server to be down or
不是这些很难确定属性，您知道我认为系统
还不满的话，你至少可以避免不良行为
is not full you could definitely get
away with bad behavior at least for a
虽然，但希望这里有足够的审核能力，如果有的话
while but the hope is that there's
strong enough auditing here that if some
证书颁发机构或日志服务器始终表现不良，人们
certificate authority or log server was
persistently badly behaved that people
会注意到监视器会注意到他们可能暂时不会做任何事情，但是
would notice the monitors would notice
they may not do anything for a while but
最终，他们会决定您知道自己要么太痛苦，要么
eventually they would decide that you
know you're either too much of a pain or
成为系统的一部分并从以下浏览器列表中删除您
to malicious to be part of the system
and delete you from the browser lists of
当然，他们将浏览器供应商划分为强大的公司，所以哇
course they split the browser vendors in
a position of quite strong power so Wow
系统通常是分散的，是的，可以有很多
the system is in general pretty
decentralized yeah there can be lots of
证书颁发机构和许多证书透明性日志服务器
certificate authorities and lots of
certificate transparency log servers
只有少数浏览器供应商，那是因为他们
there's only a handful of browser
vendors and that there because they
维护可接受的证书颁发机构和日志服务器的列表
maintain the lists of acceptable
certificate authorities and log servers
他们确实有很多力量，但是不幸的是，这就是这样，所以
they do have a lot of power and you know
it's the way it is unfortunately okay so
从证书透明性设计中脱颖而出的一件事是
things to take away from a certificate
transparency design so one thing is the
它具有非常重要的关键特性是每个人都看到相同的日志
key property it has super important is
just that everyone sees the same log
即使某些当事方是恶意的，每个人都可以看到相同的结果
even if some of the parties are
malicious either everyone sees the same
时间长了，否则他们可以从失败的证据中收集证据
long or they can accumulate evidence
from failed proofs that something's
有趣的是，这两个浏览器都在使用这些
funny is going on and because both
browsers who are using those
证书以及正在运行监视器的DNS名称的所有者，请参阅
certificates and the owners of the DNS
names who are running monitors see the
由于这些证据，监视器可以检测到问题并记录相同的日志
same log because of these proofs
the monitors can detect problems and
因此，即使浏览器实际上无法检测到虚假信息，
therefore the browser's even though the
browsers can't actually detect bogus
证书，他们至少可以确信是否存在伪造
certificates they can at least be
confident that there if there's bogus
监控器可以检测到并可能将它们放到那里的证书
certificates out there that monitors
will detect them and possibly put them
实际上，在吊销清单上，如果没有
on revocation lists actually that's
something I didn't mention if if there's
监视器的证据可以发现麻省理工学院所看到的伪造证书
evidence of a monitor spots what must be
a bogus certificate like MIT sees
他们不知道要获得麻省理工学院证书的人吗？
somebody they don't know about being
issued a certificate for MIT did you it
原来有一个预先存在的吊销服务，您可能会认为它不好
turns out there's a pre-existing
revocation service that you can put bad
浏览器检查证书，以便监视器是否看到虚假证书
certificates on that the browser's check
so if a monitor sees a bogus certificate
实际上，可以通过吊销它来有效地禁用它
it can actually be effectively disabled
by putting it on in the revocation
证书吊销系统不是证书透明性的一部分
certificate revocation system that's not
part of certificate transparency it's
已经存在了很长时间，所以关键属性是每个人都看到相同的
been around for a long time okay so the
key property is everyone sees the same
证书日志的另一件事是，如果您不能
log of certificates another thing to
take away from this is that if you can't
找出防止不良行为的方法，也许您可​​以建立一些
figure out a way to prevent bad behavior
maybe you can build something these
依赖审计而不是防止可能发现不良的可用性
usable that relies on auditing instead
of preventing that is can detect bad
事实可能会足够好之后，通常比
things after the fact that might be good
enough it's often much easier than
防止坏事，这项工作中的一些技术思想是
preventing the bad things some technical
ideas are here in this this work one is
这个我很危险的模棱两可的想法是
this idea of equivocation that I'm a big
danger is the possibility that a
恶意服务器会某种程度上提供分割视图，一个视图只能查看一组人
malicious server will sort of provide
split views one viewed one set of people
对另一组人的另一种看法，通常称为叉子或
another view to another set of people
it's usually called a fork or
模棱两可是一种重要的攻击手段
equivocation it's an important kind of
attack another property this for
事实证明，一致性属性在您担心时通常很有价值
consistency property it turns out it's
often valuable to when you're worried
关于Forks建立一旦恶意软件入侵后强制恶意服务器的系统
about Forks to build a system that
forces the malicious server once it has
组建了一个人让他们留在那把叉子上，这样它就不能通过
formed somebody to keep them on that
fork so it can't erase evidence by
消掉叉子我最后的技术诀窍是在闲聊中
erasing a fork I'm the final technical
trick is the notion of gossiping in
进行检测，因为如果参与者没有，它实际上是生成的
order to detect for because it's
actually gen if the participants don't
彼此交流实际上通常是不可能的
communicate with each other it's
actually typically not possible to
请注意，有一个叉子，所以如果要检测叉子，必须有一个
notice that there has been a fork so if
you want to detect Forks there has to be
一种方式或另一种八卦某种
one way or another
some kind of gossip some kind of
双方之间的沟通，以便他们可以比较音符并检测音叉
communication between the parties so
they can compare notes and detect forks
我们下周再看比特币和
and we'll see most of these things again
next week when we look at Bitcoin and
那就是我要说的
that's all I had to say